<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <title>mtMatt in English</title>
  
  
  <link href="http://eng.mtmatt.page/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  
  <link href="http://eng.mtmatt.page/"/>
  <updated>2021-08-21T01:20:41.915Z</updated>
  <id>http://eng.mtmatt.page/</id>
  
  <author>
    <name>mtMatt</name>
    
  </author>
  
  <generator uri="https://hexo.io/">Hexo</generator>
  
  <entry>
    <title>Ideal VS Reality</title>
    <link href="http://eng.mtmatt.page/2021/08/21/IdealVSReality/"/>
    <id>http://eng.mtmatt.page/2021/08/21/IdealVSReality/</id>
    <published>2021-08-21T00:00:00.000Z</published>
    <updated>2021-08-21T01:20:41.915Z</updated>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>What’s the distance between the ideal and relaity? Some people think it is very far. “However, it’s not as far as your imagination.” I try to think like this,but it’s so odd that I can’t believe it. After reaserch for 20 years, I found some reason why people disapoint in the world.</p><h4 id="First-politics"><a href="#First-politics" class="headerlink" title="First, politics"></a>First, politics</h4><p>In many countries, almost half people upset about the result in every election. Vote is realy useless though I can do this.</p><h4 id="Second-office-and-school"><a href="#Second-office-and-school" class="headerlink" title="Second, office and school"></a>Second, office and school</h4><p>Many childran were told that school is a small society. How would childran think about the society when they were bullied by their classmate and school system. Obviously, they would think there are massive trash in the world. And some of them will take this imagination in to there office. Dispointed and exhausted, most of the people begin upset day and night.</p><h4 id="However-that’s-not-our-all-life"><a href="#However-that’s-not-our-all-life" class="headerlink" title="However, that’s not our all life"></a>However, that’s not our all life</h4><p>It’s no saying that our life is always bad. There are always many thing great in our life. Nevertheless, how do we find our pleasure will be the most important thing.</p>]]></content>
    
    
      
      
    <summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;What’s the distance between the ideal and relaity? Some people think it is very far. “However, it’s not as far as your imagination.” I tr</summary>
      
    
    
    
    <category term="CompositionPractice" scheme="http://eng.mtmatt.page/categories/CompositionPractice/"/>
    
    
    <category term="taiwan" scheme="http://eng.mtmatt.page/tags/taiwan/"/>
    
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>Composition Practice : A Trip</title>
    <link href="http://eng.mtmatt.page/2021/08/12/EnglishCompositionPractice/"/>
    <id>http://eng.mtmatt.page/2021/08/12/EnglishCompositionPractice/</id>
    <published>2021-08-12T00:00:00.000Z</published>
    <updated>2021-08-12T04:17:57.174Z</updated>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>This was in a summer vacation, in 2010. We were going to the Janhusun Fancyworld. A fancy world lying in Yunlin. Chatting in the car, we arrived. It was a special fancy world with two part, land world and water world. We can’t go into water world because we hadn’t bought the ticket. We had a nice day until my brother’s phone lost in the Janhusun Fancyworld. We went fast to find his phone. Finally, we found his phone, and we were exhausted when we were in the hotel.<br>That’s why I don’t like to go to fancy world as a trip. I found that when anyone goes to a fancy world for a trip, they will always be exhausted and upset. But some people will feel boring when the trip without exciting things, I think maybe we should find a balance between excited and relax, or we will feel either bored or upset.</p><p>This story is not true.</p>]]></content>
    
    
      
      
    <summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;This was in a summer vacation, in 2010. We were going to the Janhusun Fancyworld. A fancy world lying in Yunlin. Chatting in the car, we </summary>
      
    
    
    
    <category term="CompositionPractice" scheme="http://eng.mtmatt.page/categories/CompositionPractice/"/>
    
    
    <category term="taiwan" scheme="http://eng.mtmatt.page/tags/taiwan/"/>
    
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>Why I don&#39;t play Brawl Stars for a short time?</title>
    <link href="http://eng.mtmatt.page/2021/07/27/Why%20I%20don&#39;t%20play%20Brawl%20Stars%20for%20a%20short%20time/"/>
    <id>http://eng.mtmatt.page/2021/07/27/Why%20I%20don&#39;t%20play%20Brawl%20Stars%20for%20a%20short%20time/</id>
    <published>2021-07-27T00:00:00.000Z</published>
    <updated>2021-07-27T12:50:37.155Z</updated>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>When summer vacation began, Brawl Stars started crashing. Red Wi-Fi all the time. I think it is because many children are playing with this game, and the server can’t bear. I won’t play this game until this problem fixed.</p>]]></content>
    
    
      
      
    <summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;When summer vacation began, Brawl Stars started crashing. Red Wi-Fi all the time. I think it is because many children are playing with th</summary>
      
    
    
    
    <category term="info" scheme="http://eng.mtmatt.page/categories/info/"/>
    
    
    <category term="BrawlStars" scheme="http://eng.mtmatt.page/tags/BrawlStars/"/>
    
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>AtCoder Beginner Contest</title>
    <link href="http://eng.mtmatt.page/2021/07/18/AtCoderBeginnerContest/"/>
    <id>http://eng.mtmatt.page/2021/07/18/AtCoderBeginnerContest/</id>
    <published>2021-07-18T00:00:00.000Z</published>
    <updated>2021-07-20T12:37:25.195Z</updated>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>After I participated three AtCoder Beginner Contests(208,209,210), I found I can just solve three to four questions. I want to solve more, but I am thinking about how to do. Maybe I should learn more DP, tree, and graph, or I need to do much more practice.</p>]]></content>
    
    
      
      
    <summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;After I participated three AtCoder Beginner Contests(208,209,210), I found I can just solve three to four questions. I want to solve more</summary>
      
    
    
    
    <category term="info" scheme="http://eng.mtmatt.page/categories/info/"/>
    
    
    <category term="AtCoder" scheme="http://eng.mtmatt.page/tags/AtCoder/"/>
    
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>Summer Vacation</title>
    <link href="http://eng.mtmatt.page/2021/07/17/SummerVavation/"/>
    <id>http://eng.mtmatt.page/2021/07/17/SummerVavation/</id>
    <published>2021-07-17T00:00:00.000Z</published>
    <updated>2021-07-18T03:23:42.992Z</updated>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Because of COVID-19, the beginning of summer vacation in Taiwan changed from 7/1 to 5/12. It sounded great to students. But it was terrible news to many parents. To me, it’s time for me to learn and practice more about programming techniques.</p>]]></content>
    
    
      
      
    <summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;Because of COVID-19, the beginning of summer vacation in Taiwan changed from 7/1 to 5/12. It sounded great to students. But it was terrib</summary>
      
    
    
    
    <category term="info" scheme="http://eng.mtmatt.page/categories/info/"/>
    
    
    <category term="taiwan" scheme="http://eng.mtmatt.page/tags/taiwan/"/>
    
  </entry>
  
</feed>
